[
  {
    "question": "What is the foundation class of your home?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "foundation",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "class-a",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "foundation-class",
        "answer": "Class A",
        "points": 1
      },
      {
        "id": "class-b",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "foundation-class",
        "answer": "Class B",
        "points": 5
      },
      {
        "id": "class-c",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "foundation-class",
        "answer": "Class C",
        "points": 10
      }
    ],
    "moreInfo": {
      "link":  "http://www.google.com/",
      "text": "FLASH"
    }
  },
    {
    "question": "What is the foundation type of your home?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "foundation",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "type-open",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "foundation-type",
        "answer": "Open Foundation",
        "points": 5
      },
      {
        "id": "type-closed",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "foundation-type",
        "answer": "Closed Foundation",
        "points": 10
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you have an open foundation, is it protected from combustion?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "foundation",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "protected-from-combustion",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "name": "open-options",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "points": 10
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If you have a closed foundation, do the vents meet criteria?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "foundation",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "vents-meet-criteria",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "name": "closed-options",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "points": 10
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of window glazing?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "windows",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "single-pane",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "window-glazing",
        "answer": "Single pane",
        "points": 1
      },
      {
        "id": "multi-pane",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "window-glazing",
        "answer": "Multi pane",
        "points": 5
      },
      {
        "id": "tempered-pane",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "window-glazing",
        "answer": "At least one tempered pane",
        "points": 10
      }
    ],
    "moreInfo": {
      "link":  "http://www.google.com/",
      "text": "FLASH"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Do the windows have non combustible screens?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "windows",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "non-combustible-screens",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "name": "open-options",
        "answer": "Yes, the windows have non combustible screens.",
        "points": 10
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do the windows have functional, fire rated shutters?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "windows",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "window-shutters",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "name": "closed-options",
        "answer": "Yes, the windows have functional, fire rated shutters.",
        "points": 10
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the roof class of your home?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "roof",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "class-a",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "roof-class",
        "answer": "Class A",
        "points": 1
      },
      {
        "id": "class-b",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "roof-class",
        "answer": "Class B",
        "points": 5
      },
      {
        "id": "class-c",
        "type": "radio",
        "name": "roof-class",
        "answer": "Class C",
        "points": 10
      }
    ],
    "moreInfo": {
      "link":  "http://www.google.com/",
      "text": "FLASH"
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "Do the valleys meet ICC 504.2.1?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "roof",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "roof-valleys",
        "name": "roof-valleys-icc",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "answer": "yes, they meet requirements.",
        "points": 25
      }
     ]
    },
  {
    "question": "Are your walls combustible?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "walls",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "walls-combustible",
        "name": "combustion",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "answer": "No, they are not combustible.",
        "points": 25
      }
     ]
    },
    {
    "question": "Does the chimney have a spark arrester?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "chimney",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "chimney-spark",
        "name": "spark-arrester",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "answer": "Yes, it has a spark arrester with 1/4 inch mesh.",
        "points": 5
      }
     ]
    },
    {
    "question": "Are the vents covered with non-corrosive/ non combustible screens with openings not exceeding 1/4 inch?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "vents",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "vents-covered",
        "name": "vents-covered",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "answer": "Yes, covered with at least 1/4 inch mesh.",
        "points": 5
      }
     ]
    },
    {
    "question": "Are the gutters non combustible?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "gutters",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "gutters-noncombustible",
        "name": "gutters-noncombustible",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "answer": "Yes, they are made of non-combustible materials",
        "points": 5
      }
     ]
    },
    {
    "question": "Are the gutters free of combustible materials?",
    "code": "wf",
    "view": "gutters",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "gutters-combustible",
        "name": "free-combustible",
        "type": "checkbox",
        "answer": "Gutters are free of combustible materials?",
        "points": 5
      }
    ]
  }
]